(Leonard:)Yeah. So?
(Sheldon:)What does that mean?
(Leonard:)Well, you know
how you're always saying
(Leonard:)that Amy is a girl
who's your friend,
(Leonard:)and not your girlfriend?
(Sheldon:)Uh-huh.
You can't say
that anymore.
(Sheldon:)Wait. What?
(Leonard:)Look, she obviously wants
(Leonard:)to take your relationship
to the next level.
(Sheldon:)I don't want
the next level.
(Sheldon:)I like this level.
(Sheldon:)Fix it for me!
(Leonard:)Me?
(Leonard:)Well, how am I supposed
to fix it?
(Sheldon:)Simple! You want a girlfriend,
(Sheldon:)Amy wants
to be someone's girlfriend.
(Sheldon:)Take her off my hands.
I give you my blessing.
(Leonard:)That is insane.
(Sheldon:)You're right.
It would never work.
(Sheldon:)Amy finds you tedious.
(Leonard:)Okay, good luck.
(Sheldon:)Wait! What am I
supposed to do?
(Leonard:)Well, have you considered
telling her how you feel?
(Sheldon:)Leonard, I'm a physicist,
not a hippie.
(Leonard:)All right, well, let me see
(Leonard:)if I can explain your situation
using physics.
(Leonard:)What would you be